workathometruth.com 2016-10-24

# Privacy - WorkAtHomeTruth

## Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy for WorkAtHomeTruth.com

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site.

We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for workathometruth.com.

This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information:

  1. Personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and
  2. Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.

We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order or as required by law.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

#### 1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

#### Registration Information

When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself.

#### Credit Card Information

If you order something directly from this site, we may request information from you on our order form.

To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).

This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

#### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

#### 2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, we use “cookies” on this site.

Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. **A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site.

For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.

Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to make the site more useful and usable for everyone.

Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies.

If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively as when you have them turned on.

#### How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

#### We Do Not Rent, Trade, or Sell Your Personal Information

We **do not** share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested or as required by law.

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities as follows:

  1. To provide the information, products and services you requested
  2. To process your payments for products and services you order from us
  3. To monitor the use of the service.
  4. To improve our content and product and service offerings
  5. To customize our site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes.

These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided on the newsletter.

#### Your Access and Control Over Information

#### Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out

This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

You can do the following at any time by contacting us using the contact information on our website:

  1. See what data we have about you, if any.
  2. Change/correct any data we have about you.
  3. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

#### What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

#### IP Address

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

#### What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or the information or content contained therein.

Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

#### Our Commitment to Data Security

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States.

The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### A Special Note About Children

Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to us.

If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

#### Change In Assets or Ownership

In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to time.

However, if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.

We will post the new policy on this page, and, if the changes allow us to use personally identifying information in ways that are different from the ways specified at the time the information was originally collected.

Each version of this privacy policy will be identified by its effective date, which you can find at the bottom of the page.

Last updated November 24, 2013.

If You're Struggling to Make Money Online [Click Here](http://michaelbrown.1minutesites.com/waht-2/) to Get Answers to All of Your Questions About Making Money Online.
